<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Increase application visibility and governance on Workshop</title>
    <link>/scenario3.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Increase application visibility and governance on Workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="/scenario3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Creating AppRegistry application with Proton</title>
      <link>/scenario3/05_map_env_resources_with_appregistry.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/scenario3/05_map_env_resources_with_appregistry.html</guid>
      <description>What are we going to do? We are going to perform the following steps:  Update environment template and deploy new version so resources will be auto-registered and metadata collected Validate that environment resources and metadata are associated with the AppRegistry application  Step-by-step guide Here are the steps you need to follow to &amp;ldquo;Create Proton environment template for AppRegistry application&amp;rdquo;.
 AWS Service Catalog AppRegistry allows you to create a repository of your applications and associated resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Auto-register resources with AppRegistry</title>
      <link>/scenario3/10_map_svc_resources_with_appregistry.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/scenario3/10_map_svc_resources_with_appregistry.html</guid>
      <description>What are we going to do? We are going to perform the following steps:  Update service templates and updated the service instances using the new service template version Associate Proton service instances resources with AppRegistry application and further enrich the application metadata Validate Proton service instances and metadata is associated with the AppRegistryApplication  Step-by-step guide Here are the steps you need to follow to update AWS Proton templates and associate resources, and it’s metadata with AppRegistry application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Query AppRegistry application metadata</title>
      <link>/scenario3/15_query_appregistry_application_metadata.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/scenario3/15_query_appregistry_application_metadata.html</guid>
      <description>What are we going to do? We are going to perform the following steps:  Query AppRegistryApplication metadata to find information cross all resources belonging to an AppRegistry application   Open the AppRegistry console and click at the EcsApp application to see more details. Observe that at this point there are a total of four resources and also four attribute groups associated with this application.
Because all the resources and metadata are linked to the application, you can query AppRegistry to find information cross resources belonging to the application.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
