<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Getting Started on Workshop</title>
    <link>/getting_started.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Getting Started on Workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="/getting_started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Connect to AWS Account</title>
      <link>/getting_started/12_connect_to_aws_account.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/getting_started/12_connect_to_aws_account.html</guid>
      <description>The following steps should be executed to apply credits if you are using your own AWS account. 1. Sign into your AWS account and click here
 📝 Note: Please ensure you enter the promotion code in the AWS account where you will run this workshop.
   Click on Redeem credit at the top right of the console.
  Enter the Promotion code issued to you by the AWS employee</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reference Architecture</title>
      <link>/getting_started/13_reference_architecture.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/getting_started/13_reference_architecture.html</guid>
      <description>Reference Architecture Current Planned </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a Workspace</title>
      <link>/getting_started/20_create_a_workspace.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/getting_started/20_create_a_workspace.html</guid>
      <description>A list of supported browsers for AWS Cloud9 is found here.
 Ad blockers, javascript disablers, and tracking blockers should be disabled for the cloud9 domain, or connecting to the workspace might be impacted. Cloud9 requires third-party-cookies. You can whitelist the specific domains.
 Launch Cloud9 in the region selected previously Navigate to the Cloud9 console.
 Select Create environment Name it MovingUpTheStackWorkshop, click Next step. Since we only need to access our Cloud9 environment via web browser, please select the Create a new no-ingress EC2 instance for environment (access via Systems Manager) under the Environment Type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure your Workspace</title>
      <link>/getting_started/25_configure_workspace.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/getting_started/25_configure_workspace.html</guid>
      <description>Follow this deep link to create an IAM role with Administrator access.
  Confirm that AWS service and EC2 are selected, then click Next: Permissions to view permissions.
  Confirm that AdministratorAccess is checked, then click Next: Tags to assign tags.
  Take the defaults, and click Next: Review to review.
  Enter movingupworkshop-admin for the Name, and click Create role.
  Click the grey circle button (in top right corner) and select Manage EC2 Instance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
